[{"answer": "my friend, its really me. Its me, you have to help, you have to find the Eye of Ra before Anubis does. Keep it, hide it, destroy it, whatever, it doesnt matter, we dont have much time", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Hey my friend, long time no see. How you doing", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why dont they try to stop her", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You dont know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Maybe", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "We are betrothed", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Is there something you wish to ask me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Indeed I was", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Indeed I was", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "A God he is not", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend says he is not dead. He is now a God", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Is he not powerful", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend, its here", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend. my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend?", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Work faster", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Its red", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The rays of the sun on the fresco  are red. my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What if its not here", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "A secret compartment inside a secret chamber", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "A secret compartment inside a secret chamber", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Why not", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I can. And I will if one more person down there is hurt", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "If you know what I am, you know very well I can wipe you from existence", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You can do nothing but stand there and utter empty threats because I know what you are", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I know you who are my friend, but you know not who I am", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You made a deal with my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I have not seen my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Full-Circle.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I do not know. One named my friend did this", "qsentId": 30}]